{
    "subject": "resource/That_Riviera_Touch",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Eric_Morecambe",
    "human_readable": "That Riviera Touch stars Eric Morecambe.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9094039797782898,
            "question": "Are there any other actors in 'That Riviera Touch' besides Eric Morecambe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.828377366065979,
            "question": "Who stars in the film 'That Riviera Touch'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7528069615364075,
            "question": "Name a film featuring Eric Morecambe."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6648250222206116,
            "question": "Is Eric Morecambe an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6376720070838928,
            "question": "What genre is 'That Riviera Touch' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6278906464576721,
            "question": "What is the name of the film starring Eric Morecambe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5865558981895447,
            "question": "Who might have directed 'That Riviera Touch'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5540476441383362,
            "question": "What is Eric Morecambe known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5166109204292297,
            "question": "Where might you find information about the plot of 'That Riviera Touch'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4542669653892517,
            "question": "When was 'That Riviera Touch' likely released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=That Riviera Touch stars Eric Morecambe.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8381_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might you find information about the plot of 'That Riviera Touch'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8381_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Eric Morecambe known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8381_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who might have directed 'That Riviera Touch'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8381_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8381_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8381_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8381_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8381_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8381_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8381_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8381_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8381_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8381_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8381_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention \"That Riviera Touch\" as a film starring Eric Morecambe and Ernie Wise, along with other information about their careers. This supports the fact that Eric Morecambe was indeed one of the stars of the movie."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention \"That Riviera Touch\" as one of the films featuring Eric Morecambe and Ernie Wise, confirming that Eric Morecambe starred in it."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}